<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeff Wong - Virtualization, Technology &amp; More</title>
    <link>https://jeffwong.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeff Wong - Virtualization, Technology &amp; More</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 12:47:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeffwong.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IOPS Limit – vSAN &amp; Virtual Hard Disk</title>
      <link>https://jeffwong.net/posts/iops-limit-vsan-virtual-hard-disk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 12:47:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffwong.net/posts/iops-limit-vsan-virtual-hard-disk/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally, I will have a technical conversation with a customer on IOPS limit so rather than repeating myself, I thought I should document it here for everyone’s benefit. Cormac Hogan had written up a good introduction to vSAN IOPS Limit storage policy that was introduced back in vSAN 6.2.
Beyond, the feature, I thought I should illustrate IOPS limit in action and highlight use cases when you would potentially want to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aligning vSAN Disk Group with Physical Setup</title>
      <link>https://jeffwong.net/posts/aligning-vsan-disk-group-with-physical-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 12:47:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffwong.net/posts/aligning-vsan-disk-group-with-physical-setup/</guid>
      <description>When designing a vSAN host, one of the consideration to increase availability is by having multiple disk groups and multiple IO controllers within a host. The obvious benefit to this would be to reduce the impact in when a disk or IO controller fails.
When a decision is made to use multiple IO controllers to drive disk groups within a vSAN host, it is important that the failure domain of such configuration is aligned with the physical setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Disks to Claim for vSAN?</title>
      <link>https://jeffwong.net/posts/no-disks-to-claim-for-vsan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:50:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffwong.net/posts/no-disks-to-claim-for-vsan/</guid>
      <description>Every so often, I will see someone hitting a speed bump setting up a disk group for vSAN. The case is the same when setting up for build your own vSAN using the disk claim wizard or VMware Cloud Foundation bring up. I thought I would do a quick write up to set it straight and point out some things to watch out for and different ways to overcome this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://jeffwong.net/posts/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:47:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffwong.net/posts/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>The Move It is now 2019 and a new chapter in my life begins. For those who know me, I had made a decision to move to the US to continue my career within the virtualization architecture space.
From January 2019, I will continue my role in the VMware Advanced Customer Engagement (ACE) team (formerly Customer Success) as a Staff Architect focusing on VMware’s Core &amp;amp; Hyper Converged Infrastructure (HCI) solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>